

Ashish Shejwal

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Profile

Frontend developer with 6+ months of experience in creating User Experience and Functional Webapp's In React, Skilled at creating Apps from Scratch, working on Existing Projects and Collaborations

Main Skills

- Javascript Es6+
- React
- Redux
- Git
- Firebase
- Figma

Contact Information

Tel: +91 9892896924

Email: ashish241.shejwal@gmail.com

Location: Thane, 400605

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/vayu02/

Employment

Junior Developer Intern at Codify Tech

July 2021 — Sep 2021

WFH Punjab

Worked on Restraunt based Webapp for non profit organisation Enhanced existing pages for better user expirence and created designs for few pages

Junior Software Developer at Webfry

Dec 2021 — Apr 2022

WFH Mumbai

Created Project from Scratch for Clients
Collaborated with CEO and team created
Webapps for Wedding and EV charging
company built complex functional UI

Education

JVM College

Jun 2020 — Apr 2021

Fy Bachelor of Computer Science